{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3518","name":"Jet's Pizza Midtown","address":"4718 Anthony Wayne Dr","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Suroor Shamoun","licenseNumber":"075120","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365","coords":"-83.07373,42.35911","geojson":{"id":"3518","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.07372813,42.359109321]},"properties":{"name":"Jet's Pizza Midtown","owner":"Suroor Shamoun","address":"4718 Anthony Wayne Dr","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"075120","establishmentid":"3518","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365","most_recent_license_date":"4/23/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4216","name":"Harmoni Garden","address":"4704 Anthony Wayne Dr","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622602","name":"Harmony Garden Cafe'","address":"4704 Anthony Wayne Dr","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622961","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Purple Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622962","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Yellow Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4092","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Blue Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622960","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Green Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4093","name":"University Prep Academy Elementary","address":"957 Holden St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"612","name":"Cafe 1 - Henry Ford Health System","address":"1 Ford Place","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"573","name":"Circa 1890 Saloon","address":"5474 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"1440","name":"Campus Diner","address":"5470 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48202"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50652","inspectionDate":"2020-02-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-02-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-02-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41920","inspectionDate":"2018-03-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-03-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"Throughout Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-03-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Just outside the","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.18","violationDescription":"The wash, rinse, and SANITIZE solutions shall be maintained clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing solutions","subItem":"wash","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-03-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"Throughout Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-03-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Smoking","subProblem":"","location":"HALLWAY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Smoke only in designated areas as restricted above."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"38436","inspectionDate":"2017-03-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of plumbing fixture","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"At the Over head spray unit ","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-04-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-03-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"walls","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Wall (back)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Ceiling fan","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3518"}}